Good morning, Saint Mia.
I've been appointed to lead
your personal guard.
Captain of the Saint's Personal Guard
Pierre
My name is Pierre.
You're the one?
Shall we proceed with your duties?
First...
There's somewhere I'd like to go.
Take me to Crown Prince Fernand.
Episode 7
"The Imprisoned Prince"
I'd never have expected you were on our side.
I could say the same.
To think someone from the crown prince
faction would be assigned to my guard...
Support for the crown prince
is common among the soldiers,
though they keep their loyalties quiet
so that Prince Julius doesn't catch wind.
It's just as Himari told me.
Prince Fernand has been sickly since birth.
The nobles who sought to promote
Prince Julius took advantage of that
to cut the crown prince
faction off at the knees.
Prince Julius treats
the soldiers as disposable.
He works us to the bone and diverts
manpower for building his golden statue.
I'm afraid there will be no
defending the kingdom like this.
I've heard you were formerly part
of Prince Fernand's personal guard.
How does he seem to be doing?
Right now...
He's waning, both in body and spirit.
It's understandable.
Prince Julius and his lackeys drove him
from the main castle into house arrest here
under the pretext of helping him recuperate.
The prince has resigned himself to his fate.
When he realized what Prince Julius was up to,
His Majesty flew into a rage
and lifted the house arrest,
but Prince Fernand has refused
to take his freedom
and hides away here in his estate to this day.
How long has it been now?
Twelve years.
Twelve years?!
This is going to take more
effort than I thought.
Prince Fernand is inside.
Girtonia has no time to lose.
I have to get through to him, no matter what!
Excuse me.
Prince Fernand.
What a pleasure it is to meet you.
I am Prince Julius's betrothed,
Mia Adenauer.
"Mia"?
I thought that his fiancée's name was Philia.
Philia is my elder sister.
Their engagement was called off so that
she could serve as saint
for our neighbors in Parnacorta.
Ah.
So we let Philia go.
I'm surprised my father made such a decision.
I'm sorry to say His Majesty has taken ill.
Prince Julius is handling affairs of state.
I see.
So he's playing at the kingship now.
I'm sure he'll get rid
of me too, soon enough.
Crown Prince of Girtonia
Fernand Girtonia
I didn't expect this.
He's not mincing words about it
yet seems completely unfazed.
So, what did you want to speak to me about?
I want you to stand against him.
To save our kingdom, I want
you to depose Prince Julius.
There are people in the kingdom
who want you to take the throne.
Just traditionalists preoccupied
with appearances,
entrenched in the notion that
the eldest son must inherit.
No, it's much more serious than that!
Girtonia is on the brink
of a terrible disaster.
If Prince Julius remains in power,
the whole kingdom will fall!
Is that how you talk about your own fiancé?
Do you hate my brother?
Yes, very much so.
But this isn't about my personal feelings.
I'm speaking as the saint of this kingdom.
I see. You're a saint too, are you?
In that case...
You should leave.
Wait, Your Highness!
Please, I need your help!
Pass.
But the disaster—
Don't care.
Honestly!
Why are both of those brothers so stubborn?!
Don't worry.
Everyone on this team is
of the crown prince faction.
I knew this wouldn't be easy,
but it's feeling almost insurmountable.
I once hinted to him that he
might go outside more often...
And?
He rejected the idea completely.
He's lost heart after
spending a decade indoors.
I know!
My first priority will be building up
his stamina and curing his illness!
Now that you mention it...
His condition improved for a time after
he took some medicine Saint Philia prepared.
Don't tell me... Did Prince Julius
sabotage that medicine, too?
No, actually.
Soon after the prince's health improved...
You made all of these, Saint Philia?!
Yes.
I want to give Prince Osvalt a present,
so I've been practicing.
He's been so kind to me since
my arrival in Parnacorta.
I mean to thank him.
That's going to make him so happy!
Do you think so?
Definitely!
I gave Mia a hairpin once before.
She did seem very pleased with it at the time.
I was thinking I'd give the prince
something he could wear as well.
Totally, totally! I just know he'll love it!
Someone almost worryingly
unconcerned with fashion
giving you a handmade accessory...
What could be more inspiring?!
Lena.
Here.
You can have this, if you'd like.
I was thinking of you when I made it.
I think it turned out quite well—
Saint Philia!
Thank you so much!
I love it! I'll treasure it forever!
It's so beautiful, Saint Philia!
Excuse me.
Saint Philia.
Himari has sent her report from Girtonia.
You again?
Your Highness.
Why did you stop taking the
medicine my sister made?
That medicine...
That was a terrible thing
your sister created.
Listen to me.
An improvement in my health now
would lead to nothing but conflict.
It would spur Julius to try to kill me.
When I took that medicine and started
feeling better, I couldn't stop shaking.
If I recover, it will restart talk of
my succession. They'll want me killed!
Why would I take that medicine knowing
what it would lead to?!
What if...
I said I would protect you?
If I could guarantee your safety,
would you take the medicine
and regain your strength?
I...
I don't know.
No, I can't do it!
I'm on your side, Your Highness.
I'll be back.
Please... never come again.
I'm sorry. But I simply
don't have time to wait.
Because I am this kingdom's saint.
The Too-Perfect Saint: Tossed Aside
by My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom
A summons from the king...
Have I done something wrong?
You don't think he's angry that
the Great Purification Circle keeps
me from my saintly duties?
Of course not!
My father just wants to meet you.
If anyone dared to speak ill of you,
I'd cut out their tongues like King Enma!
Isn't that a punishment
for liars in the afterlife?
Wow, you've heard that one?
Yeah, it's the underworld mythos of Murasame.
I was just trying to cut
the tension with a joke.
But if my father did say
something to offend you,
I'd probably take him to task.
Seeing you hurt is the
one thing I can't stand.
It gets me emotional.
I wouldn't want you
to lose face because of me.
I hope you'll refrain.
Is that a request based
on emotion? Or reason?
I'm not sure.
Rationally speaking, it would be scandalous
for anyone to take the king to task,
even his own son.
So it's most likely the latter.
I knew you'd say something like that.
Forgive me for taking so
long to meet with you.
I am Eigelstein Parnacorta,
sovereign of this realm.
I am Philia Adenauer.
My son has told me all about you.
You anticipated a potentially
catastrophic threat to our kingdom
and executed an excellent
preventative measure.
I merely did my duty as saint.
Raise your head.
If I did not reward your achievement,
Miss Philia, I would become a laughingstock.
He reminds me of Prince Osvalt somehow...
What do you wish for?
Tell me, and I will grant it
to the best of my ability.
What I wish for...
No prospect of improvement here in Girtonia.
Even with the help of the
former Saint Hildegard,
it's too much for Saint Mia to handle.
Would you like to help your sister
in our neighboring kingdom?
Y-Yes, I would!
I would very much like that!
My sister is still fighting hard
to fulfill her duties as saint,
but things are just so bad.
When I think about the possibilities...
I just feel so helpless.
What's going on?
I never realized I was so afraid...
I've been scared all this time.
Mia, I don't want to lose you.
Is this what it means... to get emotional?
F-Forgive me, Your Majesty.
Please, ignore what I—
No need for that.
I have heard your request.
I wanted to hear it from your own lips.
But I'm a saint, so...
So you're afraid to speak your own mind?
But speaking your mind is the
only way to make things happen.
Put your faith in those around
you and ask them for help.
I recommend that you become more selfish.
Osvalt.
I approve the dispatch of
Parnacorta's knights to Girtonia.
Begin talks with their leaders at once.
Understood!
Be at ease.
I'll do whatever I can
to help you, Miss Philia.
You have saved our kingdom, so it's our
responsibility to see your wishes granted.
You're good with words now and then, Father.
As for you, layabout son of mine...
Think about ways to help Miss Philia.
Yeah, right. Already on it!
Just make sure it's with
deeds, not just words.
Yeah, yeah. I hear you.
I can't believe this is happening.
But Miss Philia...
I've heard that the monsters continue
to surge outside of our borders.
At this rate, not even our knights
will be able to hold them off forever.
Yes. I've had an idea regarding that.
If you and the people
of this kingdom will allow it,
it could save Girtonia
and all of our neighbors.
Incredible.
You have another wonder in store for us?
No, I'm not the key to this plan.
It will all be up to Grace.
What...
What did you say?
The simplest way to save Girtonia
is to place a Great Purification Circle
over the entire continent.
Oh, I get it!
That would be the most effective thing.
But couldn't you have just
done that from the start?
Not even Saint Philia has enough magic power
to erect a barrier over the whole continent!
That's correct.
Which is why I want to borrow
magic power from you, Grace.
Magic power... from me?
There's an ancient ritual called
a magic-convergence spell.
It allows multiple people to pool resources
by passing magic power between them.
So Miss Grace can give you some
of her magic to enlarge the circle?
I-I can't do that!
I clearly don't have enough
magic to make that possible!
True. It is a big continent.
Even an amateur like me can
tell that doesn't add up.
You said you have older sisters who
are saints as well, didn't you?
Yes. Three of them.
Wait a minute...
I will teach you the magic-convergence spell.
I then want you to teach it to your sisters.
Of course! With magic
from five people combined,
you can make the Great Purification
Circle that much bigger.
I'm sure our knights can stave off
disaster long enough for you to do it.
Grace.
I've learned so much since
coming to this kingdom.
That if you can't do something by yourself,
you can ask someone else for help.
That if you lack what you need,
you can borrow it.
This is the answer I've learned in Parnacorta.
Please... help me.
Do you—
Saint Philia!
I'll do it!
Because there's nothing I'd love
more than being of help to you!
I'll do my part as your number one student!
Let's start practicing the ritual at once!
Thank you, Grace.
All going as planned?
My brother told me everything.
You're practicing something called
a magic-convergence spell?
Yes. She's very close to learning it.
I see.
That's right. I still don't know how
Reichardt feels about all of this...
Oh, I think it's a wonderful idea.
After all, it will put other kingdoms in
our debt with no sacrifice on our part.
It's a logical move from a saint acting
in the interests of Parnacorta.
Well...
That's right.
As I am now the saint of Parnacorta,
I'm aware that I should
always act in its interests.
However, it also makes me happy to devote
myself to my family, the people around me,
and countless others out there
whom I haven't even met.
Devoting ourselves to others
and our kingdom's prosperity is a sacred
obligation we were both born into.
I believe we may have much in common.
But I may have lost my chance to devote myself
to acting in the interest of my beloved.
Prince Reichardt...
Philia, see to it that you act
not just for the sake of others.
See that you take care of yourself as well.
Yes. I will.
Your Highness.
I'm not going to die.
If I have a sacred obligation to fulfill,
I want to live on and fulfill it
alongside the people here.
Because I love this kingdom.
She's got me beat.
Highness!
Sunshine is good for you.
It'll give you a sunny disposition, too.
I made you a picnic lunch.
I hear you rarely finish your meals.
Why are you going to such lengths?
Pierre told me...
You spend your days slaying monsters,
your nights buttering up Julius,
and in between, you come here.
You don't have time to be making lunches.
You're pushing yourself too hard.
This is a critical time.
I have to push myself!
I can't stand the thought of a
louse like him ruining my life.
Doesn't it burn you to think
someone who's trying to hurt you
is getting everything he wants?
You feel that way because you're so strong.
I'm not strong at all.
Don't pin your hopes on a weakling like me.
My father, my mother, everyone around me...
My health has only ever let them all down.
I hate it so much.
Yet at some point...
part of me began relying on it.
Useless creature.
"I'm sickly, so I don't have a choice."
"This is just how I am, so I have no choice."
I decided I'd never fare better
and gave up on trying.
I'm afraid!
I'm afraid to face what
I've run from for so long!
It's not death I fear!
I'm absolutely terrified of having to face
what a failure I've been all this time!
And that I feel this way...
Is what you hate more than anything else?
You're just like me, then.
Why are you crying?
You're a saint, aren't you?
You're strong and earnest...
Nothing like me!
Your Highness. If you fail to stand now,
you won't even be a failure.
Because failure is a right you earn
only when you fight!
If you never do more than
run away and make excuses,
you won't even rise to the level of failure!
There's nothing wrong with failing!
It means you can hold your head high
and say you didn't run from fate!
It's a wonderful thing!
I have to go.
Do you... feel the same way?
You've been disappointed in yourself
yet continued to strive.
I bet she's grown sick of me now, too.
She'll never come back here again.
I hate the thought...
Wait, that's right.
I could go to see her!
You've worn me down, Mia.
The Too-Perfect Saint Tossed Aside by
My Fiancé and Sold to Another Kingdom.
Next time, episode 8:
Next Time
Episode 8
"With You, Who Gave Me Courage"
"With You, Who Gave Me Courage."